Guide to the School of Medicine, Yale University, Records Concerning the Air Rights Garage
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
School of Medicine, Yale University, records concerning the Air Rights Garage
1969-1974
RU 453
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2
(5 boxes)
The records consist of a report and other records of the Facilities Planning Office, Yale School of Medicine, related to the air rights garage.
Yale University. School of Medicine
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 27-A (YRG 27-A), Central records and records of the dean of the Yale School of Medicine.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by subject.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of a report and other records of the Facilities Planning Office, Yale School of Medicine, related to the air rights garage.
Parking garages; Yale University -- Buildings; Yale University. School of Medicine
- Records concerning the planning of the air rights parking facility, 1969-1974; Accession 1982-A-025
  - Air Rights Garage
    - Background Material for Joint Board of Yale-New Haven Medical Center, 1974 June 18 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Background Material for Board of Directors of Yale-New Haven Hospital, 1974 June 26 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Program Analysis and Proposed Agenda, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cogen and Holt -- Air Rights Garage
    - FY 70 to FY 72 (Box 1, Folder 4 - 5)
    - FY 70 to FY 72 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - FY 73 to Feb 73 (Box 2, Folder 7 - 9)
    - Mar to Sep 73 (Box 2, Folder 10 - 12)
    - Oct 73 to Aug 74 (Box 3, Folder 13 - 16)
    - Sep 74 to -- (Box 3, Folder 17 - 18)
  - Lybrand Journal
    - v.50 nos. 3 and 4, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Parking
    - General, 1969-1973(?) (Box 4, Folder 20 - 21)
    - General, 1974- (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Interim, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Parking: Over-the-Connector
    - 1968-71 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - 1972-73 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - 1974- (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - no date (Box 4, Folder 27 - 28)
  - Applications and Reports
    - for the purchase of certain airspace over the Route 34 Highway - draft, 1972 March 3 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - to the Yale-New Haven Medical Center Joint Board, 1972 May 11 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - for the purchase or lease of certain airspace over the Route 34 Highway, 1972 October 11 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - to the Mayor of the City of New Haven, The Board of Aldermen of the City of New Haven anu The New Haven Redevelopment Agency - Draft, 1973 January (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - to the Mayor of the City of New Haven, The Board of Aldermen of the City of New Haven and The New Haven Redevelopment Agency, 1973 September 24 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - to the Connecticut Department of Environmental protection, 1974 June 1 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - to the Connecticut Health and Educational Facilities Authority - Draft, Undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - to the Connecticut Health and Educational Facilities Authority, Undated (Box 5, Folder 36)